<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>User Manual on VI Fitness</title><link>/docs/guides/</link><description>Recent content in User Manual on VI Fitness</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright (c) 2023 Hyas</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:06:50 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>/docs/guides/introduction/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/guides/introduction/</guid><description>In response to the rapid evolution of the digital era and Singapore&amp;rsquo;s commitment to becoming a tech-driven Smart Nation, our team introduces VI Fitness, a holistic web application designed to help users monitor their physical activity, diet, and overall health.</description></item><item><title>Account Creation</title><link>/docs/guides/account-creation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/guides/account-creation/</guid><description>This section will cover the account creation proccess. There are 3 ways to create an account for VI Fitness:
Manual registration Google OAuth Strava OAuth Manual Registration This is the default account creation option which can be accessed via the register page.</description></item><item><title>Workout Planner</title><link>/docs/guides/workout-planner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/guides/workout-planner/</guid><description>This section will cover the workout planner functionality.
Exercise Selection Workouts are categorised into 3 sections:
Lower Body Upper Body Core Upon selecting any of the options, Ninjas Exercise API will dynamically generate 6 workout suggetions for you to choose.</description></item><item><title>Macros Tracker</title><link>/docs/guides/macros-tracker/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/guides/macros-tracker/</guid><description>This section will cover the macros tracker functionality.
The macros tracker can be accessed via the sidebar.
Setting Daily Limits The first thing you should do when using this functionality is to calibrate your daily nutritional limits.</description></item><item><title>Strava Integration</title><link>/docs/guides/strava-integration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/guides/strava-integration/</guid><description>This section will cover the Strava Integration feature. Strava is a popular platform for tracking various physical activities. Through VI Fitness&amp;rsquo; Strava Integration feature, you can seamlessly import all your Strava activities into VI Fitness for a more comprehensive overview of your calorix expenditure.</description></item></channel></rss>